{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "English for Academic & Professional Purposes",
    "Term": "First Quarter",
    "Title": "Reflection, Reaction, and Critique Papers",
    "LastModified": "16 August 2025",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "L4-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf"
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "What is an essay of your thoughts about something that could be a movie, book, incident, etc.?",
      "answer": "Reflection Paper",
      "choices": [
        "Reaction Paper",
        "Critique Paper",
        "Reflection Paper",
        "Summary"
      ],
      "reference": "L4-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Types of Papers"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a task that requires a student to analyze information and give comments on a certain text or media?",
      "answer": "Reaction Paper",
      "choices": [
        "Reflection Paper",
        "Reaction Paper",
        "Critique Paper",
        "Summary"
      ],
      "reference": "L4-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Types of Papers"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a specific style of essay in which you identify, evaluate, and respond to an author's ideas, both positively and negatively?",
      "answer": "Critique Paper",
      "choices": [
        "Reflection Paper",
        "Reaction Paper",
        "Critique Paper",
        "Summary"
      ],
      "reference": "L4-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Types of Papers"
    },
    {
      "question": "What part of a reflection paper contains the idea and thesis statement?",
      "answer": "Introduction",
      "choices": [
        "Body",
        "Conclusion",
        "Introduction",
        "Analysis"
      ],
      "reference": "L4-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Parts of a Reflection Paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "What part of a reflection paper explains the introduction and may include quotes and passages?",
      "answer": "Body",
      "choices": [
        "Introduction",
        "Body",
        "Conclusion",
        "Comments"
      ],
      "reference": "L4-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Parts of a Reflection Paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "What part of a reflection paper wraps up the paper and describes the feeling and overall lesson?",
      "answer": "Conclusion",
      "choices": [
        "Introduction",
        "Body",
        "Conclusion",
        "Suggestion"
      ],
      "reference": "L4-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Parts of a Reflection Paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "What part of a reaction paper introduces the work to the reader by giving the name of the author and what the work is about?",
      "answer": "Details of the Work",
      "choices": [
        "The Context",
        "The Need and Reaction",
        "Details of the Work",
        "Summary"
      ],
      "reference": "L4-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Parts of a Reaction Paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "What part of a reaction paper gives the background of the piece you are reacting to?",
      "answer": "The Context",
      "choices": [
        "The Context",
        "The Need and Reaction",
        "Details of the Work",
        "Summary"
      ],
      "reference": "L4-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Parts of a Reaction Paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "What part of a reaction paper includes your opinion, thoughts, or ideas about the work?",
      "answer": "The Need and Reaction",
      "choices": [
        "The Context",
        "The Need and Reaction",
        "Details of the Work",
        "Summary"
      ],
      "reference": "L4-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Parts of a Reaction Paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "What part of a critique paper describes the work or piece you are critiquing?",
      "answer": "Introduction",
      "choices": [
        "Analysis",
        "Comments and Suggestions",
        "Introduction",
        "Summary"
      ],
      "reference": "L4-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Parts of a Critique Paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "What part of a critique paper provides the critique and detailed analysis of the work?",
      "answer": "Analysis",
      "choices": [
        "Introduction",
        "Analysis",
        "Comments and Suggestions",
        "Summary"
      ],
      "reference": "L4-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Parts of a Critique Paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "What part of a critique paper points out the things that may give improvements to the work you are critiquing?",
      "answer": "Comments and Suggestions",
      "choices": [
        "Introduction",
        "Analysis",
        "Comments and Suggestions",
        "Summary"
      ],
      "reference": "L4-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Parts of a Critique Paper"
    }
  ]
}